<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Progressive Web Apps on Learn PWA</title>
    <link>https://nitya.dev/pwa/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Progressive Web Apps on Learn PWA</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 15:19:27 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nitya.dev/pwa/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Timeline</title>
      <link>https://nitya.dev/pwa/activity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 13:55:35 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nitya.dev/pwa/activity/</guid>
      <description>Activities are listed in reverse chronological order, with most recent activity first - and grouped by year.
 2021  Jun 30, 2021 | Speaking at Web Wednesday. Jun 29, 2021 | Published this blog.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World</title>
      <link>https://nitya.dev/pwa/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Jun 2021 15:19:12 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nitya.dev/pwa/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>New to this site? Read about this project to understand the objectives and explore the learning resources on your own.
 Welcome! &amp;ldquo;Hello World!&amp;rdquo; is typically the first program you write when starting a coding journey. It helps validate your development environment and gives you the foundational structure from which you build up your knowledge.
My &amp;ldquo;Hello World&amp;rdquo; blog posts serve a similar purpose. They validate my blogging setup and workflow, and help me set the stage for what I want to achieve with the content.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About This Project</title>
      <link>https://nitya.dev/pwa/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 15:19:19 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nitya.dev/pwa/about/</guid>
      <description>Progressive Web Apps Wikipedia defines Progressive Web Apps (PWA) as:
 a type of application software delivered through the web, built using common web technologies including HTML, CSS and JavaScript. It is intended to work on any platform that uses a standards-compliant browser, including both desktop and mobile devices.
 My goal with this project is to explore the world of progressive web apps from concepts to code, from design patterns to real-world adoption.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
